<!--
  Release notes for Hisnul Muslim v1.0.20 (build 11).
  Tag names below use Google Play Console language codes. Paste each
  body into the matching locale slot in Play Console / App Store
  Connect.

  Not supported by Google Play Console (4 of our 15 in-app locales):
  Bosnian (bs), Hausa (ha), Somali (so), Yoruba (yo). Play will fall
  back to en-US for users on those locales. Translated copy for them
  is kept below for App Store Connect and in-app use.
-->

<en-US>
What's new
• You can now enable both morning and evening reminders at the same time.
• Audio recitation now plays reliably — no more "couldn't load audio".
• Search now finds category titles written in Arabic.
• On non-Arabic languages, the transliteration is shown first as the main reading text, with the translation underneath as a note. Quranic verses still show Arabic first.
• App name on the home screen now appears in your language.
• Smoother animation when you finish a zikr.
</en-US>

<ar>
ما الجديد
• يمكنك الآن تفعيل تذكيري الصباح والمساء معًا.
• تشغيل التلاوة الصوتية يعمل بشكل موثوق.
• البحث يجد الآن عناوين الفئات المكتوبة بالعربية.
• في اللغات غير العربية، يظهر النطق اللاتيني أولًا كنص أساسي للقراءة، والترجمة تحته كملاحظة. آيات القرآن تبقى بالعربية أولًا.
• اسم التطبيق على الشاشة الرئيسية يظهر بلغتك.
• حركة أنعم عند إتمام الذكر.
</ar>

<bn-BD>
নতুন কী
• এখন সকাল ও সন্ধ্যা—উভয় রিমাইন্ডার একসাথে চালু করা যাবে।
• অডিও তিলাওয়াত এখন নির্ভরযোগ্যভাবে বাজে।
• আরবিতে লেখা ক্যাটেগরির শিরোনাম এখন অনুসন্ধানে পাওয়া যায়।
• অ-আরবি ভাষায়, ট্রান্সলিটারেশন এখন মূল পাঠ্য হিসেবে উপরে দেখানো হয়, অনুবাদ নিচে নোট হিসেবে। কুরআনের আয়াত এখনও আরবি আগে দেখায়।
• হোম স্ক্রিনে অ্যাপের নাম আপনার ভাষায় দেখানো হয়।
• ফিনিশ করার সময় মসৃণ অ্যানিমেশন।
</bn-BD>

<es-ES>
Novedades
• Ya puedes activar a la vez los recordatorios de la mañana y de la noche.
• La recitación en audio funciona de forma fiable.
• La búsqueda ya encuentra los títulos de categorías escritos en árabe.
• En idiomas no árabes, la transliteración aparece primero como texto principal y la traducción debajo como nota. El Corán sigue mostrándose en árabe primero.
• El nombre de la app aparece en tu idioma.
• Animación más fluida al completar un dhikr.
</es-ES>

<fa>
چه چیز جدید است
• اکنون می‌توانید یادآور صبح و عصر را هم‌زمان فعال کنید.
• تلاوت صوتی به‌طور قابل اعتماد پخش می‌شود.
• جستجو اکنون عنوان دسته‌بندی‌های نوشته‌شده به عربی را پیدا می‌کند.
• در زبان‌های غیر عربی، حرف‌نویسی به‌عنوان متن اصلی خواندن در بالا و ترجمه به‌عنوان توضیح در پایین نمایش داده می‌شود. آیات قرآن همچنان اول عربی نشان داده می‌شوند.
• نام برنامه روی صفحه اصلی به زبان شما نمایش داده می‌شود.
• انیمیشن نرم‌تر هنگام پایان ذکر.
</fa>

<hi-IN>
क्या नया है
• अब आप सुबह और शाम दोनों रिमाइंडर एक साथ चालू कर सकते हैं।
• ऑडियो तिलावत अब विश्वसनीय रूप से चलती है।
• खोज अब अरबी में लिखे श्रेणी शीर्षक भी ढूँढ़ती है।
• गैर-अरबी भाषाओं में, लिप्यंतरण अब मुख्य पाठ के रूप में ऊपर दिखाया जाता है और अनुवाद नीचे एक नोट के रूप में। कुरआनी आयतें अभी भी अरबी पहले दिखाती हैं।
• होम स्क्रीन पर ऐप का नाम अब आपकी भाषा में दिखता है।
• ज़िक्र पूरा करने पर अधिक सहज एनिमेशन।
</hi-IN>

<id>
Yang baru
• Anda kini dapat mengaktifkan pengingat pagi dan sore secara bersamaan.
• Tilawah audio kini berfungsi dengan andal.
• Pencarian kini menemukan judul kategori yang ditulis dalam bahasa Arab.
• Pada bahasa non-Arab, transliterasi kini ditampilkan di atas sebagai teks bacaan utama, dengan terjemahan di bawah sebagai catatan. Ayat Al-Qur'an tetap menampilkan Arab di atas.
• Nama aplikasi di layar utama kini tampil dalam bahasa Anda.
• Animasi yang lebih halus saat menyelesaikan zikir.
</id>

<pt-PT>
Novidades
• Pode agora ativar os lembretes da manhã e da noite ao mesmo tempo.
• A recitação em áudio funciona de forma fiável.
• A pesquisa encontra agora os títulos de categorias escritos em árabe.
• Em idiomas não árabes, a transliteração aparece primeiro como texto principal de leitura e a tradução por baixo como uma nota. Os versículos do Alcorão continuam a mostrar árabe primeiro.
• O nome da aplicação no ecrã inicial aparece agora no seu idioma.
• Animação mais suave ao concluir um zikr.
</pt-PT>

<sw>
Mpya
• Sasa unaweza kuwasha vikumbusho vya asubuhi na jioni kwa wakati mmoja.
• Tilawa ya sauti inafanya kazi kwa uhakika.
• Utafutaji sasa unapata vichwa vya kategoria vilivyoandikwa kwa Kiarabu.
• Katika lugha zisizo za Kiarabu, maandishi ya kifonetiki sasa yanaonyeshwa juu kama maandishi makuu ya kusoma, na tafsiri chini kama maelezo. Aya za Qurani bado zinaonyesha Kiarabu kwanza.
• Jina la programu linaonyeshwa kwa lugha yako.
• Uhuishaji laini zaidi unapomaliza dhikr.
</sw>

<th>
มีอะไรใหม่
• ตอนนี้คุณสามารถเปิดใช้การแจ้งเตือนตอนเช้าและตอนเย็นพร้อมกันได้
• เสียงการอ่านทำงานได้อย่างน่าเชื่อถือ
• การค้นหาพบชื่อหมวดหมู่ที่เขียนเป็นภาษาอาหรับแล้ว
• ในภาษาที่ไม่ใช่อาหรับ คำทับศัพท์จะแสดงด้านบนเป็นข้อความหลักในการอ่าน และคำแปลด้านล่างเป็นหมายเหตุ รายการอัลกุรอานยังคงแสดงภาษาอาหรับก่อน
• ชื่อแอปบนหน้าจอหลักแสดงเป็นภาษาของคุณแล้ว
• แอนิเมชั่นที่ลื่นไหลขึ้นเมื่อทำซิกร์เสร็จ
</th>

<zh-CN>
新内容
• 现在可以同时启用早晨和傍晚两个提醒。
• 音频诵读现在可以稳定播放。
• 搜索现在可以找到用阿拉伯语书写的类别标题。
• 在非阿拉伯语界面中,音译现在显示在上方作为主要阅读文本,翻译显示在下方作为注释。古兰经条目仍以阿拉伯语优先。
• 主屏幕上的应用名称现在以您的语言显示。
• 完成迪克尔时动画更流畅。
</zh-CN>

<!--
  The following four locales are NOT supported by Google Play
  Console. Use them for App Store Connect (where supported) or
  future in-app what's-new screens.
-->

<bs>
Što je novo
• Sada možeš istovremeno uključiti jutarnji i večernji podsjetnik.
• Audio recitacija sada radi pouzdano.
• Pretraga sada pronalazi naslove kategorija napisane na arapskom.
• Na nearapskim jezicima, transliteracija se sada prikazuje na vrhu kao glavni tekst za čitanje, a prijevod ispod kao napomena. Kuranski ajeti i dalje prikazuju arapski prvi.
• Naziv aplikacije na početnom ekranu sada se prikazuje na tvom jeziku.
• Glađa animacija pri završetku zikra.
</bs>

<ha>
Sabbin abubuwa
• Yanzu kana iya kunna tunatarwar safiya da maraice tare.
• Karatun sauti yana aiki da gaskiya.
• Bincike yanzu yana samun sunayen rukunan da aka rubuta da Larabci.
• A harsuna ba na Larabci ba, rubutun harafi yanzu ana nuna shi a sama a matsayin babban rubutu na karatu, kuma fassara a ƙasa a matsayin bayani. Ayoyin Alkur'ani har yanzu suna nuna Larabci a farkon.
• Sunan manhajar a allon farko yanzu yana bayyana cikin harshenku.
• Mafi sauƙin motsi yayin kammala zikr.
</ha>

<so>
Waxa cusub
• Hadda waxaad furi kartaa xusuusiyada subaxda iyo fiidnimada hal mar.
• Akhriska codka ah wuxuu si la isku halayn karo u shaqeeyaa.
• Raadinta hadda waxay heli kartaa cinwaannada qaybaha ee Carabi ku qoran.
• Luqadaha aan Carabiga ahayn, erayada-Laatiin hadda waxay ka muuqdaan kor sida qoraalka koowaad ee akhriska, turjumaaddu hoose tahay sida qoraal-faallo. Aayaadaha Quraanka weli waxay tusayaan Carabiga horeeya.
• Magaca barnaamijka shaashadda hore hadda wuxuu ku soo baxaa luqaddaada.
• Filim-yarayn jilicsan markaad dhamaystirto dhikr.
</so>

<yo>
Kíni tuntun
• Báyìí o le mú àwọn olùrántí àárọ̀ àti alẹ́ ṣiṣẹ́ papọ̀.
• Kíkà ariwo ń ṣiṣẹ́ pẹ̀lú ìgbẹ́kẹ̀lé.
• Ìwáàrì rí àwọn àkọlé ẹgbẹ́ tí a kọ ní Lárúbáwá nísinsìnyí.
• Ní àwọn èdè tí kì í ṣe Lárúbáwá, àyípadà-akọsílẹ̀ ni a fihan ní òkè báyìí gẹ́gẹ́ bí àkọsílẹ̀ pàtàkì fún kíkà, ìtumọ̀ nísàlẹ̀ gẹ́gẹ́ bí àkọsílẹ̀-ìránti. Àwọn ẹsẹ Kurani ṣì ń fihan Lárúbáwá ní iwájú.
• Orúkọ ohun èlò lórí ojú-ìbẹ̀rẹ̀ wà ní èdè rẹ báyìí.
• Ìmúrasílẹ̀ tí ó dára síi nígbà tí o bá parí zikr.
</yo>
