<en>
What's new
• Fixed: morning and evening reminders can now both be enabled at the same time.
• Fixed: audio recitation now plays on release builds.
• Arabic category titles are now searchable.
• Non-Arabic languages: transliteration now leads, with translation as a note (Quran verses still show Arabic first).
• App launcher shows the locale's transliteration of "حصن المسلم".
• Smoother completion animation and better Android 15 edge-to-edge support.
</en>

<ar>
ما الجديد
• إصلاح: يمكن الآن تفعيل تذكيري الصباح والمساء معًا.
• إصلاح: تشغيل التلاوة الصوتية يعمل في النسخة النهائية للتطبيق.
• يمكن الآن البحث في عناوين الفئات بالعربية.
• في اللغات غير العربية: النطق اللاتيني أولًا، ثم الترجمة (آيات القرآن تبقى بالعربية أولًا).
• يظهر اسم التطبيق على الشاشة الرئيسية بترجمة صوتية لـ "حصن المسلم" حسب لغتك.
• حركة أنعم عند إتمام الذكر، ودعم محسّن لواجهة Android 15.
</ar>

<bn>
নতুন কী
• ঠিক করা হয়েছে: সকাল ও সন্ধ্যা—দুটি রিমাইন্ডার এখন একসাথে চালু করা যাবে।
• ঠিক করা হয়েছে: রিলিজ বিল্ডে অডিও তিলাওয়াত এখন বাজে।
• আরবি ক্যাটেগরির শিরোনাম এখন অনুসন্ধানযোগ্য।
• অ-আরবি ভাষায়: ট্রান্সলিটারেশন আগে, অনুবাদ একটি নোট হিসেবে নিচে (কুরআনের আয়াত এখনও আরবি আগে দেখায়)।
• লঞ্চারে "حصن المسلم"-এর স্থানীয় উচ্চারণ দেখানো হয়।
• সমাপ্তির মসৃণ অ্যানিমেশন এবং Android 15-এ আরও ভালো এজ-টু-এজ সমর্থন।
</bn>

<bs>
Što je novo
• Ispravljeno: jutarnji i večernji podsjetnici sada mogu biti istovremeno uključeni.
• Ispravljeno: audio recitacija sada radi u izdanjima za produkciju.
• Naslovi kategorija na arapskom su sada pretraživi.
• Za nearapske jezike: transliteracija je sada na vrhu, prijevod ispod kao napomena (kuranski ajeti i dalje pokazuju arapski prvi).
• Pokretač prikazuje lokalnu transliteraciju "حصن المسلم".
• Glađa animacija završetka i bolja podrška za Android 15 edge-to-edge.
</bs>

<es>
Novedades
• Corregido: ambos recordatorios (mañana y noche) ya se activan a la vez.
• Corregido: la recitación en audio funciona en versión de release.
• Los títulos de categorías en árabe ahora se pueden buscar.
• Idiomas no árabes: transliteración primero, traducción como nota (Corán sigue mostrando árabe primero).
• El lanzador muestra la transliteración de "حصن المسلم".
• Animación de finalización más fluida y mejor edge-to-edge en Android 15.
</es>

<fa>
چه چیز جدید است
• رفع شد: یادآور صبح و عصر اکنون می‌توانند هم‌زمان فعال شوند.
• رفع شد: تلاوت صوتی در نسخهٔ ریلیز کار می‌کند.
• عنوان دسته‌بندی‌ها به عربی اکنون قابل جستجو هستند.
• زبان‌های غیر عربی: ابتدا حرف‌نویسی، سپس ترجمه به‌عنوان توضیح (آیات قرآن همچنان اول عربی نشان داده می‌شوند).
• لانچر، حرف‌نویسی محلی «حصن المسلم» را نمایش می‌دهد.
• انیمیشن تکمیل نرم‌تر و پشتیبانی بهتر edge-to-edge در Android 15.
</fa>

<ha>
Sabbin abubuwa
• An gyara: yanzu za a iya kunna tunatarwar safiya da maraice tare.
• An gyara: karatun sauti yana aiki a saki na ƙarshe.
• Sunayen rukunan Larabci yanzu ana iya nemowa.
• Don harsuna ba na Larabci ba: rubutun harafi yana farkonsa, fassara a baya a matsayin bayani (ayoyin Alkur'ani har yanzu suna nuna Larabci a farkon).
• Mai ƙaddamarwa yana nuna rubutun harafi na "حصن المسلم" cikin harshenku.
• Motsi mafi sauƙi na kammalawa da kuma kyakkyawan tallafin edge-to-edge a Android 15.
</ha>

<hi>
क्या नया है
• ठीक किया गया: सुबह और शाम दोनों रिमाइंडर अब एक साथ चालू किए जा सकते हैं।
• ठीक किया गया: रिलीज़ बिल्ड में ऑडियो तिलावत अब चलती है।
• अरबी श्रेणी शीर्षक अब खोज में मिलते हैं।
• गैर-अरबी भाषाओं के लिए: लिप्यंतरण पहले, अनुवाद नीचे एक नोट के रूप में (कुरआनी आयतें अब भी पहले अरबी दिखाती हैं)।
• लॉन्चर "حصن المسلم" का स्थानीय लिप्यंतरण दिखाता है।
• पूर्ण होने पर सहज एनिमेशन और Android 15 के लिए बेहतर एज-टू-एज समर्थन।
</hi>

<id>
Yang baru
• Diperbaiki: pengingat pagi dan sore kini dapat diaktifkan bersamaan.
• Diperbaiki: tilawah audio kini berfungsi di build rilis.
• Judul kategori berbahasa Arab kini dapat dicari.
• Untuk bahasa non-Arab: transliterasi di atas, terjemahan di bawah sebagai catatan (ayat Al-Qur'an tetap menampilkan Arab di atas).
• Peluncur menampilkan transliterasi "حصن المسلم" sesuai bahasa Anda.
• Animasi penyelesaian yang lebih halus dan dukungan edge-to-edge Android 15 yang lebih baik.
</id>

<pt>
O que há de novo
• Corrigido: ambos os lembretes (manhã e noite) agora se ativam ao mesmo tempo.
• Corrigido: a recitação em áudio agora funciona em versões de release.
• Os títulos de categorias em árabe agora são pesquisáveis.
• Idiomas não árabes: transliteração primeiro, tradução como nota (Alcorão continua a mostrar árabe primeiro).
• O lançador mostra a transliteração de "حصن المسلم".
• Animação de conclusão mais suave e melhor edge-to-edge no Android 15.
</pt>

<so>
Waxa cusub
• Saxidda: xusuusiyada subaxda iyo fiidnimada labadaba waa la furi karaa.
• Saxidda: akhriska codka ah hadda wuxuu ka shaqeeyaa nuqulka la sii daayey.
• Cinwaannada qaybaha Carabiga hadda waa la raadin karaa.
• Luqadaha aan Carabiga ahayn: erayada-Laatiin horeeya, turjumaaddu hoose tahay (Quraanka weli wuxuu tusaa Carabiga horeeya).
• Bilowga wuxuu muujinayaa "حصن المسلم" oo Laatiin ah.
• Filim-yarayn jilicsan iyo taageero edge-to-edge oo ka fiican Android 15.
</so>

<sw>
Mpya
• Imerekebishwa: vikumbusho vya asubuhi na jioni vyote vinaweza kuwashwa pamoja.
• Imerekebishwa: tilawa ya sauti inafanya kazi katika toleo la kutolewa.
• Vichwa vya kategoria kwa Kiarabu sasa vinaweza kutafutwa.
• Lugha zisizo za Kiarabu: maandishi ya kifonetiki kwanza, tafsiri kama maelezo chini (aya za Qurani bado zinaonyesha Kiarabu kwanza).
• Kizinduzi kinaonyesha tafsiri ya kifonetiki ya "حصن المسلم".
• Uhuishaji laini wa kumalizia na msaada bora wa edge-to-edge kwa Android 15.
</sw>

<th>
มีอะไรใหม่
• แก้ไข: สามารถเปิดใช้การแจ้งเตือนตอนเช้าและตอนเย็นพร้อมกันได้แล้ว
• แก้ไข: เสียงการอ่านทำงานในรุ่นที่เผยแพร่
• สามารถค้นหาชื่อหมวดหมู่เป็นภาษาอาหรับได้แล้ว
• สำหรับภาษาที่ไม่ใช่อาหรับ: คำทับศัพท์ขึ้นก่อน คำแปลตามมาเป็นหมายเหตุ (รายการอัลกุรอานยังคงแสดงภาษาอาหรับก่อน)
• ตัวเปิดแอปแสดงคำทับศัพท์ของ "حصن المسلم" ตามภาษาของคุณ
• แอนิเมชั่นการทำเสร็จลื่นไหลขึ้น และรองรับ edge-to-edge บน Android 15 ดียิ่งขึ้น
</th>

<yo>
Kíni tuntun
• Atunṣe: àwọn olùrántí àárọ̀ àti alẹ́ le ṣiṣẹ́ papọ̀ báyìí.
• Atunṣe: kíkà ariwo ń ṣiṣẹ́ lórí àwọn ìtújáde.
• Àwọn àkọlé ẹgbẹ́ ní Lárúbáwá ti wà ní àwárí báyìí.
• Fún àwọn èdè tí kì í ṣe Lárúbáwá: àyípadà-akọsílẹ̀ wà ní iwájú, ìtumọ̀ wà nísàlẹ̀ gẹ́gẹ́ bí àkọsílẹ̀ (àwọn ẹsẹ Kurani ṣì ń fihan Lárúbáwá ní iwájú).
• Ojú-ìfilọlẹ̀ fihan àyípadà-akọsílẹ̀ "حصن المسلم" nínú èdè rẹ.
• Ìmúrasílẹ̀ ìparí tí ó dára síi àti àtìlẹyìn edge-to-edge dára síi fún Android 15.
</yo>

<zh>
新内容
• 修复:现在可以同时启用早晨和傍晚两个提醒。
• 修复:音频诵读在正式版本中可正常播放。
• 现在可以搜索阿拉伯语类别标题。
• 非阿拉伯语界面:音译在前,翻译作为注释在下方(古兰经条目仍以阿拉伯语为先)。
• 启动器显示您所在语言的"حصن المسلم"音译。
• 完成时动画更流畅,对 Android 15 的 edge-to-edge 支持更佳。
</zh>
